{
    "subject": "resource/Damn_Seagulls",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Helsinki",
    "human_readable": "Damn Seagulls are from Helsinki.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9413454532623291,
            "question": "Are seagulls commonly found in Helsinki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9186488389968872,
            "question": "Are there many seagulls in Helsinki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8380753397941589,
            "question": "Can seagulls be found in other cities besides Helsinki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7511784434318542,
            "question": "Where are seagulls from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5051225423812866,
            "question": "Why might someone say 'Damn Seagulls'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4260645806789398,
            "question": "What kind of animals are seagulls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3290678560733795,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of seagulls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32589536905288696,
            "question": "What is Helsinki known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2598903179168701,
            "question": "Do seagulls live near water?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22249069809913635,
            "question": "Is Helsinki a coastal city?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Damn Seagulls are from Helsinki.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2174_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do seagulls live near water?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2174_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Helsinki known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2174_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of seagulls?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2174_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2174_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Damn Seagulls is a Finnish-rock group, formed in 1997 in Helsinki (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2174/re-ranker-msmarco/18.txt), and also mention the band's connection to Finland multiple times. Therefore, the statement \"Damn Seagulls are from Helsinki\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe context information mentions that the band Damn Seagulls is from Helsinki, Finland. Therefore, the statement \"Damn Seagulls are from Helsinki\" is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}